<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xml:lang="en-us">
  <title>ExplOrozcos</title>
  <id>https://explorozcos.com/</id>
  <author>
    <name>ExplOrozcos</name>
    <uri>https://explorozcos.com/</uri>
  </author>
  <icon>https://explorozcos.com/image/brand/icon-1-1.png</icon>
  <logo>https://explorozcos.com/image/brand/icon-2-1.png</logo>
  <updated>2020-04-02T03:39:07Z</updated>
  <link rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" href="https://explorozcos.com/feed.atom" hreflang="en-us"/>
  <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://explorozcos.com/" hreflang="en-us"/>
  <entry>
    <title>Shelter In Place</title>
    <author>
      <name>Juan Orozco</name>
      <uri>https://explorozcos.com/</uri>
    </author>
    <id>https://explorozcos.com/2020/04/shelter-in-place/</id>
    <updated>2020-04-01T04:00:00Z</updated>
    <published>2020-04-01T04:00:00Z</published>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;We&#39;re doing our best to shelter in place during this epidemic. Luckily, we are mostly remote as it is anyway and we only go out for supplies and walks (while keeping within the CDC guidance of the 6-foot rule).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;North Carolina Governor, Roy Cooper, ordered us all to stay home earlier this week. He&#39;s been recommending we stay home even before that. I work remotely and the kids are homeschooled, so it was easy for us to go on lockdown way back at the beginning of March.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Supplies&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Ciri has been making meal plans for a few years now. As far as grocery shopping goes, we are pretty efficient now. Ciri goes out every two weeks and comes back with a TON of food. Not much has changed for us except that we have to be a bit more creative with meals due to some shortages.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Work&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I am luckily still employed. Although our company has been affected by the economic downturn, I&#39;m hopeful that we can weather the storm. We&#39;ve got a good group of dedicated people.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Schedule&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The first week of this shutdown saw a lot of homeschooling schedules making rounds on social media. Again, since we&#39;ve been homeschooling for years now, we already have a routine going. We started working on more walks around the neighborhood and other activities to help with cabin fever.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Fun&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I bought Pokemon Sword and pre-ordered Final Fantasy 7 Remake. That will buy us some time and help with bonding over some fun games.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This shelter-in-place has also caused a sharp growth in Pokemon Trading Cards as well. When the kids go above and beyond with their chores/routines, they earn a Pokemon TCG booster pack. (I ordered a box on eBay, so they just pull from there). I am currently the world champion (ExplOrozcos League) and Jonas is currently the 1v1v1 champion. We might start ordering specific cards in order to really fancy up our decks.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The biggest problem is the little one. She is feral. She is the one with the most energy. Before this, she was in gymnastics once a week and we were thinking about upping that to two times a week. The kids had a Spanish class they&#39;d go to and while one was in class, the other two would play in the nearby park. We&#39;re still trying to figure out something for her. It&#39;s really tough because the pollen is really bad and the bugs are also starting to get really pushy.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;That&#39;s our sit-rep for March. I&#39;m really glad how lucky we&#39;ve been through all this. I know it&#39;s not over yet, with the prediction of peak infection in two or three weeks. We&#39;ll just keep taking it one day at a time.&lt;/p&gt;</content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>Making Masks</title>
    <author>
      <name>Juan Orozco</name>
      <uri>https://explorozcos.com/</uri>
    </author>
    <id>https://explorozcos.com/2020/03/making-masks/</id>
    <updated>2020-03-26T04:00:00Z</updated>
    <published>2020-03-26T04:00:00Z</published>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Ciri received the call from Grandma a few days ago. Due to the nationwide shortage, Grandma wanted to help make masks and was checking if we had some tools she could borrow. Grandma ended up having enough equipment and supplies but Ciri decided to jump in and do her part as well.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Quickly, our dining table was overtaken with fabric, scissors, wire, elastic material, sewing machines, a laminator, a Cricut Maker, lots of Apple computing power and coffee.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://res.cloudinary.com/deo07tbou/image/upload/v1585247240/explorozcos/03-2020-making-masks-setup.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The kids, with their curiosity that is so beautiful (well, &lt;em&gt;sometimes.&lt;/em&gt; Sometimes, Mom and Dad just need a break!) asked Mom what she was up to.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It quickly became a family effort: learning to use a sewing machine; learning to cut fabric, wire, and elastic; and learning to put it all together.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://res.cloudinary.com/deo07tbou/image/upload/v1585247070/explorozcos/03-25-2020-mask-making.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A lot has changed for our way of life and although some of it might go back to normal one day, some of it will not. Yet, the kids, so far, have been robust and curious. Don&#39;t get me wrong! It isn&#39;t easy! They&#39;re still kids with lots of energy and short attention spans. But they&#39;re really trying - they &lt;strong&gt;care&lt;/strong&gt;. I can&#39;t ask for any better character trait in these kiddos than that.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So, we make masks.&lt;/p&gt;</content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>Beginnings</title>
    <author>
      <name>Juan Orozco</name>
      <uri>https://explorozcos.com/</uri>
    </author>
    <id>https://explorozcos.com/2020/03/beginnings/</id>
    <updated>2020-03-24T04:00:00Z</updated>
    <published>2020-03-24T04:00:00Z</published>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;I love sunsets. They just never seem to get old. I&#39;ve watched the sunset over the Pacific Ocean, flying tens of thousands of feet above the ground, through the mountains of Germany and throughout Europe, and back on the NC coast and over the Appalachian mountains.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Each one, every evening is magical and unique and beautiful.  Our days are numbered and I like to think that every day is an opportunity to experience the world and do good.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;That&#39;s our goal, do good. One way we&#39;ve decided to do good is to do good by our children. We want to give them various experiences of the world; see things we didn&#39;t get the chance to see; meet people we didn&#39;t get the chance to meet.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We are going to travel the States, see it in all its glory, one state at a time.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I love journaling but to put that journal in a public space feels weird - like my view on the world is more important than yours. I don&#39;t like that. What I &lt;em&gt;do&lt;/em&gt; like, is sharing. I see this journal as a way to share ideas, thoughts, and opinions. You might not agree. You might find inspiration. You might find friendship. If you say &amp;quot;Yes&amp;quot; to any of the above, well, mission accomplished.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Stay tuned as we push ourselves on this journey.&lt;/p&gt;</content>
  </entry>
</feed>
