<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xml:lang="en-us">
  <title>ExplOrozcos</title>
  <id>https://explorozcos.com/</id>
  <author>
    <name>ExplOrozcos</name>
    <uri>https://explorozcos.com/</uri>
  </author>
  <icon>https://explorozcos.com/image/brand/icon-1-1.png</icon>
  <logo>https://explorozcos.com/image/brand/icon-2-1.png</logo>
  <updated>2020-03-25T04:09:27Z</updated>
  <link rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" href="https://explorozcos.com/feed.atom" hreflang="en-us"/>
  <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://explorozcos.com/" hreflang="en-us"/>
  <entry>
    <title>Beginnings</title>
    <author>
      <name>Juan Orozco</name>
      <uri>https://explorozcos.com/</uri>
    </author>
    <id>https://explorozcos.com/03-23-2020-beginnings/</id>
    <updated>2020-03-24T04:00:00Z</updated>
    <published>2020-03-24T04:00:00Z</published>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;I love sunsets. They just never seem to get old. I&#39;ve watched the sunset over the Pacific Ocean, flying tens of thousands of feet above the ground, through the mountains of Germany and throughout Europe, and back on the NC coast and over the Appalachian mountains.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Each one, every evening is magical and unique and beautiful.  Our days are numbered and I like to think that every day is an opportunity to experience the world and do good.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;That&#39;s our goal, do good. One way we&#39;ve decided to do good is to do good by our children. We want to give them various experiences of the world; see things we didn&#39;t get the chance to see; meet people we didn&#39;t get the chance to meet.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We are going to travel the States, see it in all its glory, one state at a time.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I love journaling but to put that journal in a public space feels weird - like my view on the world is more important than yours. I don&#39;t like that. What I &lt;em&gt;do&lt;/em&gt; like, is sharing. I see this journal as a way to share ideas, thoughts, and opinions. You might not agree. You might find inspiration. You might find friendship. If you say &amp;quot;Yes&amp;quot; to any of the above, well, mission accomplished.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Stay tuned as we push ourselves on this journey.&lt;/p&gt;</content>
  </entry>
</feed>
